It's that I don't want to talk much about the subject to
Es que no quiero hablar mucho del tema a
anyone because it is Then I appear in the
nadie porque es Entonces ya salgo en
clip of uncle shur of Javier Olive idra of so and so and so and so and so it doesn't matter what he says it doesn't matter what he does it doesn't matter how he
clip de tío shur de Javier Olive idra de
says it it's that he is pointless he is pointless
lo diga es que es pointless es pointless
because these people live off this he lives off harassing
porque esta gente vive de esto vive de
distorting manipulating
acosar tergiversar manipular información
third party information so that people take
de terceros para que la gente pille
sides take enemies and are
lados pille enemigos y estén
constantly involved in drama I mean there are
constantemente metidos en el drama O sea
people whose job is literally to
hay gente que su trabajo es literalmente
screw people over creating drama Poor thing
a la gente crear drama Pobrecita
eh of course we get into dramas
eh claro es que entamos los dramas la
poor Abi who is not looking for any
pobre Abi que es que no busca ningún
drama poor Abi who is a girl who
drama la pobre Abi que es una chica que
flies very very fast with a super
pasa muy muy volando con el perfil super
low profile eh I mean Abi flies with a
bajito eh o sea Abi vuela con un perfil
super low profile calm down she doesn't mess with
super bajito tranquilita no se mete con
anyone the girl is super discreet okay you have to
nadie la muchacha super discreta vale
see that they distort things
hay que ver que distorsionan las cosas
to put people against each other eh be
para ponerle a la gente en contra eh ser
eh Really the [ __ ] [ __ ] and the scum
eh De verdad la y la calaña
of the internet How
de internet Cómo
Wait Wait I was coming very chill
Espérate Espérate que venía muy chill yo
eh
eh